A Guide to the Newsmap, World News of the Week, A. M. S. Bulletins Collection, 1942-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- World News of the Week, 1944-1949 (Box 3-5)
  - Monday, October 25, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 9
  - Monday, November 1, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 10
  - Monday, November 8, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 11
  - Monday, November 15, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 12
  - Monday, November 22, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 13
  - Monday, November 29, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 14
  - Monday, December 6, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 15
  - Monday, December 13, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 16
  - Monday, December 20, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 17
  - Monday, December 27, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 18
  - Monday, January 3, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 19
  - Monday, January 10, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 20
  - Monday, January 17, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 21
  - Monday, January 24, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 22
  - Monday, January 31, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 23
  - Monday, February 7, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 24
  - Monday, February 14, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 25
  - Monday, February 21, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 26
  - Monday, February 28, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 27
  - Monday, March 7, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 28
  - Monday, March 14, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 29
  - Monday, March 21, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 30
  - Monday, March 28, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 31
  - Monday, April 4, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 32
  - Monday, April 11, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 33
  - Monday, April 18, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 34
  - Monday, April 25, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 35
  - Monday, May 2, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 36
  - Monday, May 9, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 37
  - Monday, May 16, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 38
  - Monday, May 23, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 39
  - Monday, May 30, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 40
  - Monday, June 6, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 41
  - Monday, June 13, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 42
  - Monday, June 20, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 43
  - Monday, June 27, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 44
  - Monday, July 4, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 45
  - Monday, July 11, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 46
  - Monday, July 18, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 47
  - Monday, July 25, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 48
  - Monday, August 1, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 49
  - Monday, August 8, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 50
  - Monday, August 15, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 50
  - Monday, September 10, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 2
  - Monday, September 17, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 3
  - Monday, September 24, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 4
  - Monday, October 1, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 5
  - Monday, October 22, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 8
  - Monday, November 8, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 11
  - Monday, November 15, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 12
  - Monday, November 22, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 13
  - Monday, November 29, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 14
  - Monday, December 6, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 15
  - Monday, December 13, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 16
  - Monday, December 20, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 17
  - Monday, December 27, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 18
  - Monday, January 3, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 19
  - Monday, January 10, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 20
  - Monday, January 17, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 21
  - Monday, January 24, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 22
  - Monday, January 31, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 23
  - Monday, February 7, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 24
  - Monday, February 14, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 25
  - Monday, February 21, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 26
  - Monday, February 28, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 27
  - Monday, March 7, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 28
  - Monday, March 14, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 29
  - Monday, March 21, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 30
  - Monday, March 28, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 31
  - Monday, April 4, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 32
  - Monday, April 11, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 33
  - Monday, April 18, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 34
  - Monday, April 25, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 35
  - Monday, May 2, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 36
  - Monday, May 9, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 37
  - Monday, May 16, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 38
  - Monday, May 23, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 39
  - Monday, May 30, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 40
  - Monday, June 6, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 41
  - Monday, June 13, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 42
  - Monday, June 20, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 43
  - Monday, June 27, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 44
  - Monday, July 4, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 45
  - Monday, July 11, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 46
  - Monday, July 18, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 47
  - Monday, July 25, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 48
  - Monday, August 1, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 49
  - Monday, August 8, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 50
  - Monday, August 15, 1949, Vol. 11, No. 51
- Other Publications, 1945-1969
  - World Aeronautical Chart, 3rd edition, August 1955 (Box 5)
  - Status of Aerial Photography, September 1964 (Box 5)
  - U. S. Army, Corps of Engineers, Army Map Service, January 17, 1969 (Box 5)
  - The Army Map Service, Its Mission, History and Organization, 1960 (Box 5)
  - A. M. S. Memorandum, Grids and Magnetic Declinations, Fourth Edition, February 1945 (Box 5)
  - A. M. S. Memorandum, Geographical Names for Military Maps, Second Edition, July 1945 (Box 5)
  - Defense Intelligence Agency, Charting and Geodetic Terms, February, July 1967 (Box 5)
  - Geodesy for the Layman, Glossary of Mapping, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Culture Features, Section XI (2 copies) (Box 5)
  - War Deparment, Memorandum for the Information & Education Center (Box 5)